(Raj:)Do you think the elastic woman
in The Incredibles...
(Raj:)...needs to use birth control
or can she just be a diaphragm?
(Howard:)Well, that's it. We're officially
out of things to talk about.
(Penny:)We're home.
It's 10:00. Where have you been?
(Sheldon:)We stayed
for the California Adventure water show.
(Sheldon:)It was pure Disney magic.
-I was gonna see that with him.
-How was I to know that?
(Sheldon:)It's all right. I'll see it again with you.
I have food here. You were gonna call.
(Penny:)-I know, I know.
-I can still eat.
(Penny:)No. You already threw up once.
Go put on your p.j.'s and brush your teeth.
(Sheldon:)Okay, but just don't fight.
(Leonard:)-We're not fighting.
-Just go.
Aren't you gonna thank Penny
for taking you?
(Sheldon:)Thank you, Penny.
(Penny:)You're welcome, sweetie.
(Leonard:)Want a cup of coffee?